Abitibi ManagementUnit O
River ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Paul ContactName B-PERSON
Fantin ContactName I-PERSON
R ContactName I-PERSON
P ContactName I-PERSON
F ContactName I-PERSON
 ContactName E-PERSON

 Phone O
705 Phone O
544 Phone O
2828 Phone O
ext Phone O
223 Phone O
paul Email O
fantin Email O
frmg Email O
ca Email O

Algoma ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Vince ContactName B-PERSON
Strack ContactName E-PERSON

Clergue Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Inc Company I-ORG
 Company E-ORG
Silviculture Title O
and Title O
Operations Title O
Forester Title O
 Phone O
705 Phone O
942 Phone O
7706 Phone O
ext Phone O
1 Phone O

vince Email O
strack Email O
clergue Email O
com Email O


Big ManagementUnit O
Pic ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Carmelo ContactName B-PERSON
Notarbartolo ContactName E-PERSON
Nawiinginokiima Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O

 Phone O
807 Phone O
229 Phone O
8118 Phone O
ext Phone O
11 Phone O
carmelo Email O
notarbartolo Email O
nfmcforestry Email O
ca Email O


Gordon ManagementUnit O
Cosens ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Darren ContactName B-PERSON
Ethier ContactName E-PERSON

Rayonier Company B-ORG
Advanced Company I-ORG
Materials Company I-ORG
Inc Company I-ORG
 Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
North Title O
Ontario Title O
West Title O
FRM Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
337 Phone O
9784 Phone O
darren Email O
ethier Email O
rayonieram Email O
com Email O

Hearst ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Desneiges ContactName B-PERSON
Larose ContactName E-PERSON
Hearst Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Inc Company I-ORG
 Company E-ORG

General Title O
Manager Title O
 Phone O
705 Phone O
362 Phone O
4464 Phone O
ext Phone O
1 Phone O
705 Phone O
372 Phone O
3848 Phone O

d_larose Email O
hearstforest Email O
com Email O


Magpie ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
John ContactName B-PERSON
Peluch ContactName E-PERSON

Wawa Company B-ORG
District Company E-ORG
MNRF Title O
District Title O
Manager Title O
 Phone O
705 Phone O
856 Phone O
4703 Phone O
john Email O
peluch Email O
ontario Email O
ca Email O

Martel ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Chris ContactName B-PERSON
Grant ContactName E-PERSON

Tembec Company S-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
North Title O
Ontario Title O
East Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
864 Phone O
3002 Phone O
chris Email O
grant Email O
tembec Email O
com Email O


Nagagami ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Carlo ContactName B-PERSON
Bin ContactName E-PERSON
Nagagami Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Ltd Company I-ORG
 Company E-ORG

President Title O

 Phone O
807 Phone O
868 Phone O
2426 Phone O
carlobin Email O
hornepaynelumber Email O
com Email O

Nipissing ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Mark ContactName B-PERSON
Lockhart ContactName E-PERSON

mlockhart Email O
nipissingforest Email O
com Email O

Northshore ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

William ContactName B-PERSON
Moryto ContactName E-PERSON

Northshore Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Inc Company I-ORG
 Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
869 Phone O
4020 Phone O
ext Phone O
263 Phone O
william Email O
moryto Email O
eacom Email O
ca Email O


Pineland ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Jennifer ContactName B-PERSON
Tallman ContactName E-PERSON

EACOM Company B-ORG
Timber Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG

Chief Title O
Forester Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
267 Phone O
3339 Phone O
ext Phone O
227 Phone O
jennifer Email O
tallman Email O
eacom Email O
ca Email O


Romeo ManagementUnit O
Malette ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Chris ContactName B-PERSON
Grant ContactName E-PERSON

Tembec Company S-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
North Title O
Ontario Title O
East Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
864 Phone O
3002 Phone O

chris Email O
grant Email O
tembec Email O
com Email O

Romeo ManagementUnit O
Malette ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Alan ContactName B-PERSON
Thorne ContactName E-PERSON
Tembec Company S-ORG

Chief Title O
Forester Title O
Ontario Title O
 Phone O
705 Phone O
360 Phone O
1280 Phone O
alan Email O
thorne Email O
tembec Email O
com Email O


Spanish ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Jennifer ContactName B-PERSON
Tallman ContactName E-PERSON
EACOM Company B-ORG
Timber Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG

Chief Title O
Forester Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
267 Phone O
3339 Phone O
ext Phone O
227 Phone O
jennifer Email O
tallman Email O
eacom Email O
ca Email O


Sudbury ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Mark ContactName B-PERSON
Lockhart ContactName E-PERSON

 Phone O
705 Phone O
752 Phone O
5430 Phone O
ext Phone O
21 Phone O
705 Phone O
499 Phone O
6275 Phone O
mlockhart Email O
nipissingforest Email O
com Email O


Temagami ManagementUnit O
Mitch ContactName B-PERSON
Baldwin ContactName E-PERSON

North Company B-ORG
Bay Company I-ORG
District Company E-ORG

MNRF Title O
District Title O
Manager Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
475 Phone O
5599 Phone O

mitch Email O
baldwin Email O
ontario Email O
ca Email O

Timiskaming ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O

Yves ContactName B-PERSON
Vivier ContactName E-PERSON
Timiskaming Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Alliance Company I-ORG
Inc Company I-ORG
 Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O

 Phone O
705 Phone O
544 Phone O
2828 Phone O
705 Phone O
544 Phone O
3368 Phone O

yves Email O
viver Email O
frmg Email O
ca Email O


White ManagementUnit O
River ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Don ContactName B-PERSON
Larmer ContactName E-PERSON

White Company B-ORG
River Company I-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Products Company I-ORG
LP Company E-ORG

Superintendent Title O
Forest Title O
Planning Title O
and Title O
Compliance Title O
 Phone O
807 Phone O
822 Phone O
1818 Phone O
ext Phone O
220 Phone O
don Email O
larmer Email O
wrfp Email O
ca Email O


tom Email O
ratz Email O
resolutefp Email O
com Email O

